<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mental health on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/mental-health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mental health on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 08:49:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/mental-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 37: Rosh Hashanah</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/17/week-37-rosh-hashanah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 08:49:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/17/week-37-rosh-hashanah/</guid>
      <description>Cooler temperatures! After the hottest week I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced in months, things were back to comfortable Summer weather. By the time I&amp;rsquo;m writing this the sky is gray and it&amp;rsquo;s raining, but this week&amp;rsquo;s weather was cheerful and moderate. On Tuesday and Wednesday I gave two big UX workshops at week to help coworkers understand how they can use UX in their daily work. I&amp;rsquo;ve been giving workshops for well over a decade, always trusting my instinct to figure out what a particular group or context required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 36: Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/10/week-36-homecoming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:21:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/10/week-36-homecoming/</guid>
      <description>IT IS HOT STOP CLIMATE CHANGE NOW. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve seen hotter days this year than week 36. Getting out of a hot shower and feeling equally wet fifteen minutes later. Lemonade barely wanting to walk outside. The sun beaming so feriously we can&amp;rsquo;t keep the windows open. Thank you, Jesus, but please make it cooler. There&amp;rsquo;s something sweet about seeing Amsterdam through the eyes of friends from abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two things true</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/06/two-things-true/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/06/two-things-true/</guid>
      <description>I saw a guy on Monday that I went on a date with once. It was one of those whimsical dates. We had fish by the sea. It felt like coming home a little bit. I think the world was trying to introduce me to something for which I wasn&amp;rsquo;t ready yet. Looking back, that date, more than the others, prepared me for Anja. Looking back through butterfly effect glasses, it might as well have been him.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
