<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>friends on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/friends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in friends on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:21:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/friends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 36: Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-09-10-week-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:21:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-09-10-week-36/</guid>
      <description>IT IS HOT STOP CLIMATE CHANGE NOW. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve seen hotter days this year than week 36. Getting out of a hot shower and feeling equally wet fifteen minutes later. Lemonade barely wanting to walk outside. The sun beaming so feriously we can&amp;rsquo;t keep the windows open. Thank you, Jesus, but please make it cooler. There&amp;rsquo;s something sweet about seeing Amsterdam through the eyes of friends from abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Pride means to me in 2023</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-07-22-pride-walk-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-07-22-pride-walk-2023/</guid>
      <description>Nienke, Mehdi, an anonymous friend, and I attend the annual Pride March. It&amp;rsquo;s the city&amp;rsquo;s first two-week Pride festival in Amsterdam, each week organized by a different organization. With a naturally intersectional and radically-inclusive interpretation of the term &amp;ldquo;queer&amp;rdquo;, I am pleased Queer Amsterdam is taking care of the annual Pride Walk.&#xA;On Friday, I tell colleagues over office drinks why we still need Pride. The fact that I had to write &amp;ldquo;an anonymous friend&amp;rdquo; instead of the name of a person I love and admire illustrates my point beautifully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Nienke, you should have a website</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-26-dear-nienke-you-should-have-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-26-dear-nienke-you-should-have-a-website/</guid>
      <description>Every time I embark on a journey towards a published post about why it&amp;rsquo;s good to have a website, I get lost in the reality of personal details. Everyone has different reasons for believing something. Aiming to take them all into account doesn&amp;rsquo;t help me write anything that feels worthwhile and not like a derivative1.&#xA;It feels much more relevant to focus my attention on specific people. In this case I&amp;rsquo;m focusing my attention on you, Nienke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meeting Yana and DJ</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-11-meeting-yana-and-dj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-11-meeting-yana-and-dj/</guid>
      <description>What I love most about today&amp;rsquo;s snapshot is the despair I can see in Lemonade&amp;rsquo;s eyes even when her entire body is a background blur. DJ is a calm 12-year-old dog, and Lemonade was thrilled to see another dog in our home for the first time, but her energy level was high enough that I eventually brought her back to her crate. It was right in time, too, because the afternoon light filling the living room made for a nice little portrait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A very Mathilde visit</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-08-a-very-mathilde-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-08-a-very-mathilde-visit/</guid>
      <description>Much like last year, I&amp;rsquo;m so excited for Mathilde to visit our house that I get a headache just thinking about it. We&amp;rsquo;ve known each other 23 years, and, by miracle, our friendship is both acclimatized to our adult lives and as full of energy and curiosity as it was when we met in our first year of secondary school.&#xA;She comes bearing gifts: seeds for the garden, dyke poetry, David Sedaris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A phone call with an old friend</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-16-a-phone-call-with-an-old-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-16-a-phone-call-with-an-old-friend/</guid>
      <description>Happiness today is the ease with which the nun gives me his phone number. Paul is an old friend, or really an old friend of my ex, and we haven&amp;rsquo;t spoken in eight years.&#xA;I had emailed him late last year, missing our kitchen table conversations over coffee and cigarettes. His enormous house, a former school, functioning as his private art studio / gallery. He had replied right away, saying &amp;ldquo;my phone number is still the same&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking with Annelie</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-02-02-walking-with-annelie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-02-02-walking-with-annelie/</guid>
      <description>Walking with Annelie is coffee indoors today. We&amp;rsquo;ve told each other we need to go on more walks. She asks if we should dress warmly for the cold, wet park, or if we should just grab a table inside. Normally at this hour, Coffee Company is packed to the brim with digital nomads, so &amp;ldquo;dress for cold, hope for warmth&amp;rdquo; I say. Miraculously, there are two tables from which we can choose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 15: Ironic</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2022-04-17-week-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2022-04-17-week-15/</guid>
      <description>Brushing my teeth on Friday morning, I think about the weekend ahead, secretly complaining that my social engagements will keep me from getting the rest I need. Then I remember Easter Monday. The true marker of my mid-thirties is the excitement I feel at the prospect of a bed, and nothing but it.&#xA;I hold a baby this week, one of my favorite ones. His face has two states that exist simultaneously: the one of utter shock and surprise only newborns can have, and the one that reminds you that babies know everything about the world and forget it as soon as they start to speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kind agents</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2021-06-26-kind-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2021-06-26-kind-agents/</guid>
      <description>The weather is great, infection rates are down, and the Dutch government loosened Covid restrictions. Masks are no longer required in public indoor spaces. I&amp;rsquo;m at Basquiat waiting to catch up with a friend, and an Irish woman strikes up a conversation.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I like to sit here late in the afternoon to watch the sun set between the buildings. I can&amp;rsquo;t take much sun, I have Irish skin, you know.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misanthropy anew</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2012-08-11-misanthropy-anew/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2012-08-11-misanthropy-anew/</guid>
      <description>My friend Paul is a very wise man. Last week, as he drove O. and me home after a morning of catching up at the house / workshop / gallery / former school building in which he dwells, he said:&#xA;I would love to have another life, just so I could spend it cursing at everything, and everyone.&#xA;The negative character of this man is self-evident. He&amp;rsquo;s as much a misanthrope as he is an engaging full of life and stories.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
