<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Israel-Hamas War on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/israel-hamas-war/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Israel-Hamas War on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 10:16:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/israel-hamas-war/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 46: Osama</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-11-19-week-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 10:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-11-19-week-46/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m making an attempt this week to make my weeknotes more of a personal record rather than a performance of how exciting my week is. What I&amp;rsquo;ve written answers the question I might ask myself seven years from now: what was life like this week? I went on the road for on-site research on Tuesday, and was delighted by the particular nursing home that we visited. It seems many Dutch healthcare organizations have understood that environments that resemble the real-life environments of patients contribute to their overall wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The artificial borders of climate activism</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-11-13-artificial-borders-of-climate-activism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 10:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-11-13-artificial-borders-of-climate-activism/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday at the Climate March, someone shouted &amp;ldquo;From the river to the sea, Palestine will be free&amp;rdquo;. It was an unfortunate thing. A clean example of the climate changing instantaneously among 85,000 activists.&#xA;I was there for four reasons:&#xA;My definition of God is &amp;ldquo;science is indescribably beautiful and we must respect her&amp;rdquo; I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a more regrettable waste of tax money than having to spend it on health issues we can prevent if only we take better care of our environment I have a weak spot for an activist friend, who, through stealth influencing, had instilled in me a deep sense of FOMO about the event The Dutch carnival season had kicked off on November 11, and I was in the mood for a parade The phrase was understandable coming from the Palestinian woman.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
