<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travel on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travel on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Norway et al</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-08-17-norway-et-al/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-08-17-norway-et-al/</guid>
      <description>After two weeks in Scandinavia, it&amp;rsquo;s clear: we are both too Dutch for proper recycling. Secretly hoarding our trash to avoid a reprimanding from our AirBnb host as he hovers over his six-compartment recycling bin, we continue our trip from rural Sweden to Copenhagen looking for a public recycling station.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Imagine if we got so nervous about doing it wrong that we ended up just dumping these bags by the roadside&amp;rdquo; I say to Anja.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overheard in July</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2021-07-27-overheard-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2021-07-27-overheard-in-july/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do you want this problem to get smaller or bigger?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I still love you, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing it from behind this line.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Blaue Augen sind besser als braune Augen&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Blue eyes are better than brown eyes&amp;rdquo;, 10-year-old brown-eyed German boy to his blue-eyes brother at the Okura Hotel breakfast bar)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A believable truth</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2021-07-18-a-believable-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2021-07-18-a-believable-truth/</guid>
      <description>I never get much reading done unless I&amp;rsquo;m sleeping elsewhere. Most often, I associate sleeping elsewhere with having time off, and having time off means I&amp;rsquo;m away from a computer screen. This frees up time for reading.&#xA;Anja had booked a suite for my birthday at Okura, and six months after I turn 33, Covid measures are finally so mild that we actually get to do it. It&amp;rsquo;s on the sixteenth floor, overlooking the Amsterdam Centre and West Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2016-03-16-she/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2016-03-16-she/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Slept a little, had a midnight snack, went in for a bathroom break. Slept some more. Basically the life of a four-year-old&amp;rdquo; she says, and she tells me about her flight to Stockholm. She has been sleeping poorly lately; I say &amp;ldquo;lately&amp;rdquo; but I only met her last month, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know what her sleep hygiene is, although she says &amp;ldquo;it has improved since I began falling asleep in your arms&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
