<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pandemic on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/pandemic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pandemic on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/pandemic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Walking with Annelie</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/02/walking-with-annelie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/02/walking-with-annelie/</guid>
      <description>Walking with Annelie is coffee indoors today. We&amp;rsquo;ve told each other we need to go on more walks. She asks if we should dress warmly for the cold, wet park, or if we should just grab a table inside. Normally at this hour, Coffee Company is packed to the brim with digital nomads, so &amp;ldquo;dress for cold, hope for warmth&amp;rdquo; I say. Miraculously, there are two tables from which we can choose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 47: Booster</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/11/27/week-47-booster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/11/27/week-47-booster/</guid>
      <description>I forgot how the COVID booster can make you feel as though, temporarily, the world may well be ending. I got it earlier this week, and it left me with a sore arm and that dreadful, ridiculous sensation that accompanies a flu that lasts a week too long. I mimic my late stepfather, who used to wimper like a puppy whenever he got a cold. I still do well to limit my hours of screen time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 13: Recruiting</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/02/week-13-recruiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/02/week-13-recruiting/</guid>
      <description>It has been snowing in Amsterdam. As the years go by, I&amp;rsquo;m having trouble understanding whether I&amp;rsquo;m experiencing the effects of global warming, or whether I&amp;rsquo;ve never paid attention to what was always in front of me until now. It is likely a combination of the two. Either way, it is sad to see Amsterdammers retreat into their homes after two weeks of shorts and drinks in the sun.&#xA;At work Leeruniek&amp;rsquo;s Product team is hiring, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the one taking care of the recruitment process for two engineering and one design role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overheard in July</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/27/overheard-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/27/overheard-in-july/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do you want this problem to get smaller or bigger?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I still love you, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing it from behind this line.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Blaue Augen sind besser als braune Augen&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Blue eyes are better than brown eyes&amp;rdquo;, 10-year-old brown-eyed German boy to his blue-eyes brother at the Okura Hotel breakfast bar)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kind agents</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/06/26/kind-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/06/26/kind-agents/</guid>
      <description>The weather is great, infection rates are down, and the Dutch government loosened Covid restrictions. Masks are no longer required in public indoor spaces. I&amp;rsquo;m at Basquiat waiting to catch up with a friend, and an Irish woman strikes up a conversation.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I like to sit here late in the afternoon to watch the sun set between the buildings. I can&amp;rsquo;t take much sun, I have Irish skin, you know.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aging: part one</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/03/12/aging-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/03/12/aging-part-one/</guid>
      <description>When I was a child, no physical activity brought me more delight than inline skating. I had a wonderful pair of skates; silver, neon pink, and teal, snuggly fitting my feet. I felt limitless on those wheels, cruising all around the neighborhood, learning tricks in the grocery store parking lot, and distance skating past farms and fields.&#xA;For the past five years, I&amp;rsquo;ve been telling myself that I should get a new pair of skates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: Home office</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/17/week-2-home-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/17/week-2-home-office/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at keeping it a secret: my favorite time in the week is when A works from home. We spent the past month building a home office in a one-bedroom apartment, and I&amp;rsquo;m happy about the result. Monday is Uni day for her. I find it endearing that her Statistics course is throwing her for a loop a little bit.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Work is so great!&amp;rdquo; I think to myself on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The end of cute</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020/12/28/the-end-of-cute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020/12/28/the-end-of-cute/</guid>
      <description>I have a friend&#xA;who is so mad&#xA;at the pandemic&#xA;that he went on&#xA;a six-day crack bender&#xA;just to prove it&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve deleted the numbers&#xA;of all my dealers as well as the&#xA;man who changed my mind&amp;rdquo;&#xA;he tells me&#xA;His eyes reflect a me&#xA;judging him for him&#xA;and I am&#xA;I have deleted numbers&#xA;deleted apps&#xA;food&#xA;versions of my&#xA;self&#xA;myself&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Also I saw your</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That time we were the first to get Covid</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020/09/20/that-time-we-were-the-first-to-get-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020/09/20/that-time-we-were-the-first-to-get-covid/</guid>
      <description>Amsterdam&amp;rsquo;s patient zero is a woman who just happens to have spent early 2020 in the north of Italy. She has a son who attends the high school which just happens to be Anja&amp;rsquo;s place of employment. Anja is the first person I know to be infected with Covid 19. I am the second.&#xA;Working in travel technology, my experience of the outbreak of Covid 19 was colored by coworkers wondering by the water cooler what all the fuss was about.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
