<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blogging on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/blogging/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blogging on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 10:16:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/blogging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So, about this Scriptogr.am</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/05/so-about-this-scriptogr.am/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 10:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/05/so-about-this-scriptogr.am/</guid>
      <description>I am notorious for never grasping how many people know how much about what. To save myself from any further embarrassment I won&amp;rsquo;t spend my time here telling you what the app is about. The team does that nicely over here. I do think I have something to say about what Scriptogr.am came exactly at the right time for me.&#xA;As we more further down the line of Web 2.0 and slowly into the abyss that is Web 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The old sharing</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/13/the-old-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/13/the-old-sharing/</guid>
      <description>I am nostalgic about the way the Web used to be. I miss the handcrafted blogs that I used to visit, and the intimate windows they gave me into the lives of strangers.&#xA;I miss that I knew all the domain names by heart. It is a phantom pain of sorts; an unrest in the tip of my fingers reminding me I no longer need to make series of key combinations to find those personal public spaces, some more arts-and-craftsy than others, because most of them are gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On keeping a journal</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2012/08/31/on-keeping-a-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2012/08/31/on-keeping-a-journal/</guid>
      <description>The only journal I’ve ever been able to successfully keep is a photo journal. Not so much the one-book or one-website type, but more so a simply collection of visual anecdotes, encounters and experiences. My first website was called www.doyoulikemytightsweater.com. It was a HTML-based one-photo-per-page website that I updated very frequently. Ever since the domain expired and I got a little sick of getting pervy emails (I should have known), I had never owned a photo website that I loved so much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considerations</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2009/09/27/considerations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2009/09/27/considerations/</guid>
      <description>It was indeed great while it lasted, until about three weeks ago. Churning out little posts, coming up with fun tidbits, roaming the streets of Eindhoven with a little noteback. Getting feedback. Compliments. Your mother&amp;rsquo;s cousins&amp;rsquo; daughters&amp;rsquo; coworkers are reading your blog. And then university life begins. And there is time for nothing.&#xA;So here&amp;rsquo;s a change of strategy, and of pace.&#xA;This website will be featuring different forms of content from now on.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
