<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anja on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/anja/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Anja on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/anja/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anja&#39;s ceramics course</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-16-anjas-ceramics-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-16-anjas-ceramics-course/</guid>
      <description>Today, Lemonade and I visited Studio Pansa Amstel, where Anja has spent the last seven Sundays learning how to work a ceramics wheel. It&amp;rsquo;s quite the adventure for her, and I love seeing her dive into a new field that&amp;rsquo;s so different from her day-to-day life and work. Their motto is &amp;ldquo;dirty hands, clear mind&amp;rdquo;, and that certainly seems to be the case for Anja.&#xA;I saw dozens of gorgeous little cups in the making, each with a unique maker&amp;rsquo;s mark and the intricate details only found in things that were crafted by hands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 10: Outings</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-12-week-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-12-week-10/</guid>
      <description>It snowed a few times this week and I was as baffled as I always am to see it happening in March. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a great understanding of what the weather&amp;rsquo;s supposed to do in a given period of the year. After two weeks of cocooning, we&amp;rsquo;ve finally been taking Lemonade out to various places. I aim to take her out at least once a day, usually to the park or a walk around the block.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog park</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-22-dog-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-22-dog-park/</guid>
      <description>My attempt to lure both Anja and myself outside for some fresh air and a walk was thwarted as soon as I learned the place was out of my favorite bubble tea. We strolled to Flevopark, in my hand an ice cream cone, and on my face the disappointment of a toddler who can’t be satisfied.&#xA;The park has a wide field that allows loose dogs to roam freely in the off-season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-recognizer</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-20-super-recognizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-20-super-recognizer/</guid>
      <description>On occasion, Anja will compliment me on my ability to recognize people. I don’t know when I first noticed it myself, but there are actors I recognize even if they played minor characters in an episode of a show I watched 15 years ago. Or I might point out that woman I saw on the bus before COVID hit to a confused Anja.&#xA;I’m learning it’s not a very common trait because of the scoffing sound I make whenever Anja confuses Keira Knightly and Daisy Ridley, or Michelle Pfeiffer and Meg Ryan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prospective dog owners</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-19-prospective-dog-owners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-19-prospective-dog-owners/</guid>
      <description>I’m in that supremely annoying stage of prospective dog ownership where I casually interrogate dog owners at parties, curious about their pet’s behavior and the techniques employed, and then silently judge them for their mistakes, exchanging contemptuous glances with Anja in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 51: The piano</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2022-12-25-week-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2022-12-25-week-51/</guid>
      <description>Happy Hanukkah and/or Christmas to those who celebrate! Even though our house is (reluctantly) multi-religious, we forgot just about every tradition we were ever taught for this time of the year. On Hanukkah Eve, Anja said &amp;ldquo;where are the tea lights?&amp;rdquo;, but we had no luck finding them to produce a makeshift chanukiah. Probably for the best. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind that we didn&amp;rsquo;t put up a Christmas tree, but I did find myself missing our outrageous ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That time we were the first to get Covid</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2020-09-20-that-time-we-were-the-first-to-get-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2020-09-20-that-time-we-were-the-first-to-get-covid/</guid>
      <description>Amsterdam&amp;rsquo;s patient zero is a woman who just happens to have spent early 2020 in the north of Italy. She has a son who attends the high school which just happens to be Anja&amp;rsquo;s place of employment. Anja is the first person I know to be infected with Covid 19. I am the second.&#xA;Working in travel technology, my experience of the outbreak of Covid 19 was colored by coworkers wondering by the water cooler what all the fuss was about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2016-03-16-she/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2016-03-16-she/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Slept a little, had a midnight snack, went in for a bathroom break. Slept some more. Basically the life of a four-year-old&amp;rdquo; she says, and she tells me about her flight to Stockholm. She has been sleeping poorly lately; I say &amp;ldquo;lately&amp;rdquo; but I only met her last month, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know what her sleep hygiene is, although she says &amp;ldquo;it has improved since I began falling asleep in your arms&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
