<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>milestones on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/milestones/</link>
    <description>Recent content in milestones on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/milestones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Two weeks with a dog</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/08/two-weeks-with-a-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/08/two-weeks-with-a-dog/</guid>
      <description>Lemonade, Lemonade, Lemonade. Who knew I would ever become a dog person? Two weeks ago, we picked up our corgi Lemonade Zelda Loulé. There was a torrent of research both Anja and I did to prepare for this puppy. There was a birth announcement card. A godmother was appointed. Here are some things I learned after two weeks with a dog.&#xA;The ROI of good research Anja and I are both blessed with a-type personalities and a propensity for thorough investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 years sober</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/05/02/3-years-sober/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/05/02/3-years-sober/</guid>
      <description>On May 2, 2018, as we got off the plane from Stockholm, completing our visit with Anneli and Milan, I said calmly to Anja:&#xA;I think I may try not drinking for a week or so.&#xA;Nothing dramatic had happened in Stockholm. We had just returned from a midweek staying with friends in the city, followed by a couple days at a cozy cabin in the woods. It was my first time meeting these friends and they are wonderful people: two kind-hearted, curious journalists and their young daughter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Airtrade, hello Leeruniek</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020/11/01/goodbye-airtrade-hello-leeruniek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020/11/01/goodbye-airtrade-hello-leeruniek/</guid>
      <description>After five years of learning, falling on my face, making friends, and getting to know the travel industry, the time has come for me to say goodbye to Airtrade. This year, the travel industry took a huge blow, with many of the small and big clients we&amp;rsquo;ve acquired over the years in serious heavy water. What&amp;rsquo;s more, five years is a good run, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you say?&#xA;My next adventure is taking me even deeper into making tools for people at work, and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more thrilled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That time we were the first to get Covid</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020/09/20/that-time-we-were-the-first-to-get-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020/09/20/that-time-we-were-the-first-to-get-covid/</guid>
      <description>Amsterdam&amp;rsquo;s patient zero is a woman who just happens to have spent early 2020 in the north of Italy. She has a son who attends the high school which just happens to be Anja&amp;rsquo;s place of employment. Anja is the first person I know to be infected with Covid 19. I am the second.&#xA;Working in travel technology, my experience of the outbreak of Covid 19 was colored by coworkers wondering by the water cooler what all the fuss was about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women&#39;s March Amsterdam</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2017/01/25/womens-march-amsterdam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2017/01/25/womens-march-amsterdam/</guid>
      <description>Proudly nasty, I joined Anja, my mother-in-law Sauci, and millions of others around the world last Saturday to attend the Women&amp;rsquo;s March. Museum Square in Amsterdam was full of pussy hats, face paint, smiling faces, and righteous indignation.&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t often attend protests, not in the last place because I&amp;rsquo;m cautious about negative media outlets that often ridicule protesters, but I loved being a part of this day. I have no idea what&amp;rsquo;s in store with this American presidency, but I imagine it can&amp;rsquo;t be very positive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
