<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>overheard on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/overheard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in overheard on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/overheard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overheard in July</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021-07-27-overheard-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021-07-27-overheard-in-july/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do you want this problem to get smaller or bigger?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;I still love you, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing it from behind this line.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Blaue Augen sind besser als braune Augen&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Blue eyes are better than brown eyes&amp;rdquo;, 10-year-old brown-eyed German boy to his blue-eyes brother at the Okura Hotel breakfast bar)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2016-03-16-she/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2016-03-16-she/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Slept a little, had a midnight snack, went in for a bathroom break. Slept some more. Basically the life of a four-year-old&amp;rdquo; she says, and she tells me about her flight to Stockholm. She has been sleeping poorly lately; I say &amp;ldquo;lately&amp;rdquo; but I only met her last month, so I don&amp;rsquo;t know what her sleep hygiene is, although she says &amp;ldquo;it has improved since I began falling asleep in your arms&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to live for God</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2015-01-16-explanation-for-the-bible/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2015-01-16-explanation-for-the-bible/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve heard someone compare it to the relationship between a parent and a child. I imagine a child wanting to create a birthday card for his mother, opting to draw her portrait on the cover. Does that child draw a lifelike portrait of his mother? No, but it sure is endearing. I just want to draw the most beautiful portrait I can with the colors I got from my Mother.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
