<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bible on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/bible/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bible on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/bible/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When Jesus sent out his Twelve</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021-07-12-when-jesus-sent-out-his-twelve/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021-07-12-when-jesus-sent-out-his-twelve/</guid>
      <description>This was written as part of Vine &amp;amp; Fig&amp;rsquo;s Sunday Scripture reflection project.&#xA;When Jesus sent out his Twelve, He told them: “Whatever place does not welcome you or listen to you, leave there and shake the dust off your feet in testimony against them.” If you’re not welcomed, not listened to, quietly withdraw. Don’t make a scene. Shrug your shoulders and be on your way.&#xA;Last week, a friend of ours in the Vine &amp;amp; Fig community asked me to proofread a letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family, or notes from the battlefield</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021-01-01-family-or-notes-from-a-battlefield/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021-01-01-family-or-notes-from-a-battlefield/</guid>
      <description>As soon as she hands you the gift&#xA;you know it’s another one&#xA;“Trans Life Survivors”&#xA;says the cover&#xA;“Merry Christmas!”&#xA;says your sister&#xA;you have only been using&#xA;they/them pronouns&#xA;in private&#xA;for a year or so&#xA;it’ll look so beautiful next to&#xA;the ex-gay book&#xA;your other sister presented to you&#xA;on your birthday last month&#xA;At family dinner you&#xA;spend bathroom breaks in your&#xA;childhood bedroom&#xA;five in total</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of bridges and neighbors</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020-11-29-of-bridges-and-neighbors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020-11-29-of-bridges-and-neighbors/</guid>
      <description>When I first learned that ‘pontifex’, Pope Francis’ Twitter account, is Latin for ‘bridge builder’, I was entirely delighted. “How wonderful”, I thought, “that our institution sees the value in a Pope who builds bridges between the Church and the rest of humanity.”&#xA;When I look at myself with kind eyes, I dare to see the ways in which I myself help build these bridges. As a queer facilitator, I’m part of the leadership team at Vine &amp;amp; Fig, a community for affirming LGBTQIA+ Catholics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hell is other people</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020-11-22-hell-is-other-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020-11-22-hell-is-other-people/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s meditate on us scattered sheep today, shall we? After all, if not scattered, then what are we? It has become a running gag in our household. I will be reading the New York Times, shaking my fist at whomever is responsible for the failed separation of Church and State. Or perhaps I&amp;rsquo;m mad at those who think their Christian inclination allows them to dictate what happens in other people&amp;rsquo;s bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The benefit of discontent</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020-09-25-the-benefit-of-discontent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020-09-25-the-benefit-of-discontent/</guid>
      <description>If you are at all involved in queer Catholic Twitter, you know that last week was a riot. Cause célèbre was an unexpected shout-out from Pope Francis:&#xA;Pope Francis told a group of parents of L.G.B.T. children yesterday that “God loves your children as they are” and “the church loves your children as they are because they are children of God.” — America Magazine&#xA;My timeline was flooded, and understandably so: the Catholic Church hasn&amp;rsquo;t profiled itself as a boundary-pushing institution on very many occassions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clobber</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020-05-13-clobber/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020-05-13-clobber/</guid>
      <description>This was originally published as part of the Vine &amp;amp; Fig &amp;ldquo;Pray Tell&amp;rdquo; project.&#xA;She sounds quite chipper once she makes it to the telephone. ‘Hey dear!’ it sounds. ‘Happy Mother’s Day&amp;rsquo;, I go. A few years ago, when I decided that I was going to transition into low contact mode with my mother, I couldn’t have imagined that Mother’s Day was going to be like this.&#xA;As many countries celebrate moms today, we remember that, on Mother’s Day last year, we saw my stepfather leave for the hospital, never to return again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to live for God</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2015-01-16-explanation-for-the-bible/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2015-01-16-explanation-for-the-bible/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve heard someone compare it to the relationship between a parent and a child. I imagine a child wanting to create a birthday card for his mother, opting to draw her portrait on the cover. Does that child draw a lifelike portrait of his mother? No, but it sure is endearing. I just want to draw the most beautiful portrait I can with the colors I got from my Mother.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
