<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>work on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in work on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 27: Haven</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-07-09-week-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-07-09-week-27/</guid>
      <description>This week, I attended my first Gerimedica party. It’s great to know I can expect a big celebration every year, and not just for the company’s sweet sixteen. It confirmed what I already know: great vibe, great taste, great people. I went to Bar Bario on Saturday for a meet-up called Hair Haven, which fosters connection between people with curly hair. Again, I was struck by how welcoming the space is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 26: Keti Koti</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-07-01-week-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-07-01-week-26/</guid>
      <description>Two months of onboarding have rushed by in a blink. The new job is absolutely wonderful: the people are great, the work is complex and important, and the office itself is perhaps the finest I&amp;rsquo;ve ever worked at. I joined this company because the challenges they have seemed interesting to me. I&amp;rsquo;m very pleased that, two months in, it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to think that, at one point in time, these challenges weren&amp;rsquo;t also mine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That was January 2023</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-31-that-was-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-31-that-was-january/</guid>
      <description>January flew, flew by, I tell you. We started with &amp;ldquo;wow, 2023 already, let&amp;rsquo;s have a chill time this year, hey what&amp;rsquo;s on Netflix?&amp;rdquo; and at the time of writing everything is different:&#xA;Things are not chill, because we&amp;rsquo;re preparing ourselves, our lives, and our house for our first-ever puppy Both our work lives are unexpectedly bustling and busy We cancelled Netflix I&amp;rsquo;ve been saying for years that I&amp;rsquo;d be willing to pay 100 euros a month for a single, all-encompassing international streaming platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>`alt` text culture</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-13-alt-text-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-01-13-alt-text-culture/</guid>
      <description>More than any other time in my online life am I aware of the value of alt text. I make a point to write image descriptions whenever I can. Kind strangers with a variety of accessibility needs have been helping me understand how to best capture my interpretation of an image. I&amp;rsquo;ve come to regard alt text as the secret side bar I get to have with blind people and others who need it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Airtrade, hello Leeruniek</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2020-11-01-goodbye-airtrade-hello-leeruniek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2020-11-01-goodbye-airtrade-hello-leeruniek/</guid>
      <description>After five years of learning, falling on my face, making friends, and getting to know the travel industry, the time has come for me to say goodbye to Airtrade. This year, the travel industry took a huge blow, with many of the small and big clients we&amp;rsquo;ve acquired over the years in serious heavy water. What&amp;rsquo;s more, five years is a good run, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you say?&#xA;My next adventure is taking me even deeper into making tools for people at work, and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more thrilled.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
