<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>indieweb on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/indieweb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in indieweb on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 08:49:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/indieweb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 37: Rosh Hashanah</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-09-17-week-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 08:49:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-09-17-week-37/</guid>
      <description>Cooler temperatures! After the hottest week I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced in months, things were back to comfortable Summer weather. By the time I&amp;rsquo;m writing this the sky is gray and it&amp;rsquo;s raining, but this week&amp;rsquo;s weather was cheerful and moderate. On Tuesday and Wednesday I gave two big UX workshops at week to help coworkers understand how they can use UX in their daily work. I&amp;rsquo;ve been giving workshops for well over a decade, always trusting my instinct to figure out what a particular group or context required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-07-02-08-54-00/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 08:54:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-07-02-08-54-00/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m humbled by learning that my words are the introduction of someone else&amp;rsquo;s biography.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-26-16-29-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 16:29:36 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-26-16-29-36/</guid>
      <description>Just noticed this UI change, Barry, I like it!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-26-12-53-00/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 12:53:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-26-12-53-00/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this week I found myself in line at a coffee place giving my friend a very passionate speech in response to her question &amp;ldquo;why would anyone have a website?&amp;rdquo;. I always marvel at people who don&amp;rsquo;t share this sentiment with us, James. Nice to meet you!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Nienke, you should have a website</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-26-dear-nienke-you-should-have-a-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-04-26-dear-nienke-you-should-have-a-website/</guid>
      <description>Every time I embark on a journey towards a published post about why it&amp;rsquo;s good to have a website, I get lost in the reality of personal details. Everyone has different reasons for believing something. Aiming to take them all into account doesn&amp;rsquo;t help me write anything that feels worthwhile and not like a derivative1.&#xA;It feels much more relevant to focus my attention on specific people. In this case I&amp;rsquo;m focusing my attention on you, Nienke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-17-10-24-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 10:24:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-17-10-24-39/</guid>
      <description>This is precisely what I love about webmentions, the return to the cozy web!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-08-10-35-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 10:35:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-08-10-35-51/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-05-07-41-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 07:41:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-05-07-41-50/</guid>
      <description>I love this essay, Simone. Fully embracing the very IndieWeb concept of a personal website has helped me shake this feeling of FOMO, I imagine the same way it did for you. Don&amp;rsquo;t be hard on yourself, though, we all fell for this concept, and many of us still do. If society presents something as a way to solve a problem, most people will eventually try it. And while it does solve some problems, it also creates others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-04-12-31-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 12:31:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-03-04-12-31-29/</guid>
      <description>Darn Barry, I feel like 2023 is throwing you for quite a loop. Ever since you wrote about you getting laid off I think about you every now and then. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry this happened last week, although I must say I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s a lucky thing those divvies wanted to get a break-in early bird special.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-02-03-09-16-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 09:16:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-02-03-09-16-47/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m quite excited at the prospect of an impromptu, Kimberly Hirsch-is-in-the-Netherlands-inspired IndieWeb meet-up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notes on my web mastery</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2022-11-26-notes-on-my-web-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2022-11-26-notes-on-my-web-mastery/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been making some great progress with my personal website. While I normally don&amp;rsquo;t engage in technical ballets on the goings-on of this website, I feel it&amp;rsquo;s relevant to document what I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt and done, if only for posterity.&#xA;Tools Jekyll: as is often the case for me, this site is built using my favorite flat-file content management system Github: hosts the code for this website Netlify: serves the content to my website Obsidian: I write in a single Obsidian vault obsidian-git: helps me manage the version control of my Obsidian content Push git subdirectory as branch: a Github action that lets me publish a part of the content of my Obsidian vault to a separate repository Git submodule: my separate repository is pulled into my website&amp;rsquo;s code base Netlify build hook: every day, Netlify looks for new content and publishes it to my website Why this is great I hold the strong belief that tools don&amp;rsquo;t matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 15: Ironic</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2022-04-17-week-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2022-04-17-week-15/</guid>
      <description>Brushing my teeth on Friday morning, I think about the weekend ahead, secretly complaining that my social engagements will keep me from getting the rest I need. Then I remember Easter Monday. The true marker of my mid-thirties is the excitement I feel at the prospect of a bed, and nothing but it.&#xA;I hold a baby this week, one of my favorite ones. His face has two states that exist simultaneously: the one of utter shock and surprise only newborns can have, and the one that reminds you that babies know everything about the world and forget it as soon as they start to speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The old sharing</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2021-07-13-the-old-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2021-07-13-the-old-sharing/</guid>
      <description>I am nostalgic about the way the Web used to be. I miss the handcrafted blogs that I used to visit, and the intimate windows they gave me into the lives of strangers.&#xA;I miss that I knew all the domain names by heart. It is a phantom pain of sorts; an unrest in the tip of my fingers reminding me I no longer need to make series of key combinations to find those personal public spaces, some more arts-and-craftsy than others, because most of them are gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A lifetime without representation</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-12-20-a-lifetime-without-representation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/posts/2023-12-20-a-lifetime-without-representation/</guid>
      <description>My friend and I reunite after 18 months. I missed him dearly, but once we sit down for ramen we can both tell it&amp;rsquo;s like we were there yesterday. I talk about him often. He&amp;rsquo;s the person who was so discombobulated by Dutch white innocence, that he felt more comfortable going back to the Middle East to live in the closet. He&amp;rsquo;s doing better now. No more crack, and the spinning class is surprisingly inclusive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
