<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pets on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/pets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pets on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/pets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meeting Yana and DJ</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-04-11-meeting-yana-and-dj/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-04-11-meeting-yana-and-dj/</guid>
      <description>What I love most about today&amp;rsquo;s snapshot is the despair I can see in Lemonade&amp;rsquo;s eyes even when her entire body is a background blur. DJ is a calm 12-year-old dog, and Lemonade was thrilled to see another dog in our home for the first time, but her energy level was high enough that I eventually brought her back to her crate. It was right in time, too, because the afternoon light filling the living room made for a nice little portrait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The cat</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-04-10-the-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-04-10-the-cat/</guid>
      <description>Life sure is different now that we&amp;rsquo;ve gotten Lemonade on a proper walking schedule. She still feels most comfortable going potty on the puppy pads we have on our balcony, but she absolutely loves going out and exploring the neighborhood.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m surprised by how well she walks on a loose leash, and how few issues we&amp;rsquo;ve had with the stuff she puts in her mouth. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to make most use of her imprint period, and that means familiarizing her with as many different things as possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A very Mathilde visit</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-04-08-a-very-mathilde-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-04-08-a-very-mathilde-visit/</guid>
      <description>Much like last year, I&amp;rsquo;m so excited for Mathilde to visit our house that I get a headache just thinking about it. We&amp;rsquo;ve known each other 23 years, and, by miracle, our friendship is both acclimatized to our adult lives and as full of energy and curiosity as it was when we met in our first year of secondary school.&#xA;She comes bearing gifts: seeds for the garden, dyke poetry, David Sedaris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 11: Meeting Patrick</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-26-week-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-26-week-11/</guid>
      <description>I got to meet one of my Internet heroes this week: Patrick Rhone and his family were on a Europe trip, and I was lucky enough to catch the planning stage on his blog right in time to extend an invitation. We spent a rainy Monday evening in de Jordaan at Cafe de Tuin, talking ye olde Internet productivity culture, the arts, politics, hopes and dreams, and how his teenage daughter apparently woke up one night singing &amp;ldquo;raise a glass to freedom&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 10: Outings</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-12-week-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-12-week-10/</guid>
      <description>It snowed a few times this week and I was as baffled as I always am to see it happening in March. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a great understanding of what the weather&amp;rsquo;s supposed to do in a given period of the year. After two weeks of cocooning, we&amp;rsquo;ve finally been taking Lemonade out to various places. I aim to take her out at least once a day, usually to the park or a walk around the block.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-10-09-03-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 09:03:06 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-10-09-03-06/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what it says about me that I find it annoying when people don&amp;rsquo;t recognize that my puppy is a corgi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two weeks with a dog</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-08-two-weeks-with-a-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-08-two-weeks-with-a-dog/</guid>
      <description>Lemonade, Lemonade, Lemonade. Who knew I would ever become a dog person? Two weeks ago, we picked up our corgi Lemonade Zelda Loulé. There was a torrent of research both Anja and I did to prepare for this puppy. There was a birth announcement card. A godmother was appointed. Here are some things I learned after two weeks with a dog.&#xA;The ROI of good research Anja and I are both blessed with a-type personalities and a propensity for thorough investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog park</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-22-dog-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-22-dog-park/</guid>
      <description>My attempt to lure both Anja and myself outside for some fresh air and a walk was thwarted as soon as I learned the place was out of my favorite bubble tea. We strolled to Flevopark, in my hand an ice cream cone, and on my face the disappointment of a toddler who can’t be satisfied.&#xA;The park has a wide field that allows loose dogs to roam freely in the off-season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prospective dog owners</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-19-prospective-dog-owners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-19-prospective-dog-owners/</guid>
      <description>I’m in that supremely annoying stage of prospective dog ownership where I casually interrogate dog owners at parties, curious about their pet’s behavior and the techniques employed, and then silently judge them for their mistakes, exchanging contemptuous glances with Anja in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sneak preview</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-15-sneak-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-15-sneak-preview/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything about the dog</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-12-everything-about-the-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-12-everything-about-the-dog/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard? Anja and I are getting a dog. It was up in the air for a little while, but we got the confirmation yesterday that we&amp;rsquo;ll get first pick of a nest of eight adorable little Pembroke - Cardigan corgi mixes. We&amp;rsquo;re meeting the puppies for the first time on Sunday. Are you crying? I&amp;rsquo;m crying.&#xA;2022 showed me that there are serious drawbacks to being an A type personality.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
