<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amsterdam on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/amsterdam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amsterdam on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:21:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/amsterdam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 36: Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/10/week-36-homecoming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:21:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/10/week-36-homecoming/</guid>
      <description>IT IS HOT STOP CLIMATE CHANGE NOW. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve seen hotter days this year than week 36. Getting out of a hot shower and feeling equally wet fifteen minutes later. Lemonade barely wanting to walk outside. The sun beaming so feriously we can&amp;rsquo;t keep the windows open. Thank you, Jesus, but please make it cooler. There&amp;rsquo;s something sweet about seeing Amsterdam through the eyes of friends from abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 33: Landing</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/20/week-33-landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/20/week-33-landing/</guid>
      <description>The first week back at work is fairly quiet, I even found myself on the verge of boredom at one point. Organically, this makes me feel bad, but I remind myself that weeks before and after holidays tend to have this effect on my life. I tell myself I&amp;rsquo;m just landing. No one can convince me the municipality of Amsterdam isn’t using major construction projects to show tourists how crap the city can be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Pride means to me in 2023</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/07/22/what-pride-means-to-me-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/07/22/what-pride-means-to-me-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>Nienke, Mehdi, an anonymous friend, and I attend the annual Pride March. It&amp;rsquo;s the city&amp;rsquo;s first two-week Pride festival in Amsterdam, each week organized by a different organization. With a naturally intersectional and radically-inclusive interpretation of the term &amp;ldquo;queer&amp;rdquo;, I am pleased Queer Amsterdam is taking care of the annual Pride Walk.&#xA;On Friday, I tell colleagues over office drinks why we still need Pride. The fact that I had to write &amp;ldquo;an anonymous friend&amp;rdquo; instead of the name of a person I love and admire illustrates my point beautifully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight of ten</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/04/09/eight-of-ten/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/04/09/eight-of-ten/</guid>
      <description>When I first set foot in the Old Catholic Church to attend an All Saints service, I knew I had found a special place. Today is the third time I make it to their service, which is always on the second Sunday of the month.&#xA;It just so happens that this second Sunday falls on Easter, and it&amp;rsquo;s perhaps because of this that the service is more crowded than previous times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Saints Amsterdam</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/12/all-saints-amsterdam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/12/all-saints-amsterdam/</guid>
      <description>She blesses Anja, me, and a handful of other people who carved out time in their Sunday evenings to come to Church. I have never been inside this particular church building before, and chuckle at how new the Old Catholic decor is: in imagery and candle lighting possibilities it&amp;rsquo;s reminiscent of the average Dutch Roman Catholic church. Its white walls and central heating tell me something different.&#xA;You may think I chose this church because the woman blessing us is Desmond Tutu&amp;rsquo;s daughter, the Reverend Canon Mpho Tutu van Furth, and because Anja and I can&amp;rsquo;t help but fangirl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why doesn&#39;t the crosswalk work?</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/23/why-doesnt-the-crosswalk-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/23/why-doesnt-the-crosswalk-work/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a woman who runs a bookshop in De Bijlmer. She has kind eyes that make you want to curl up with a book and a cup of tea. Often when I&amp;rsquo;m there, she offers just that: tea, and a place to quiet down and dive into an interesting title. She&amp;rsquo;s running a fine business over there, Cole Verhoeven is.&#xA;Aside from bookshop owner she&amp;rsquo;s also a writer. I love the work she does at One World, where she articulates strong perspectives on antiracism and equity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog park</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/22/dog-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/22/dog-park/</guid>
      <description>My attempt to lure both Anja and myself outside for some fresh air and a walk was thwarted as soon as I learned the place was out of my favorite bubble tea. We strolled to Flevopark, in my hand an ice cream cone, and on my face the disappointment of a toddler who can’t be satisfied.&#xA;The park has a wide field that allows loose dogs to roam freely in the off-season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 13: Recruiting</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/02/week-13-recruiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/02/week-13-recruiting/</guid>
      <description>It has been snowing in Amsterdam. As the years go by, I&amp;rsquo;m having trouble understanding whether I&amp;rsquo;m experiencing the effects of global warming, or whether I&amp;rsquo;ve never paid attention to what was always in front of me until now. It is likely a combination of the two. Either way, it is sad to see Amsterdammers retreat into their homes after two weeks of shorts and drinks in the sun.&#xA;At work Leeruniek&amp;rsquo;s Product team is hiring, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the one taking care of the recruitment process for two engineering and one design role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 12: Bonsoihoir</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/03/26/week-12-bonsoihoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/03/26/week-12-bonsoihoir/</guid>
      <description>The tourists are back in town. Lots of Germans with face masks. I suppose we&amp;rsquo;re all beginning to venture out into the world again, just a bit closer to home. Anja and I are considering taking the ferry to Norway. Apparently you can camp virtually anywhere in that country, as long as you &amp;ldquo;leave it cleaner than you found it&amp;rdquo; and make sure you&amp;rsquo;re gone after two days. At this point, we&amp;rsquo;re vastly underestimating how attached we are to luxury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A believable truth</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/18/a-believable-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/18/a-believable-truth/</guid>
      <description>I never get much reading done unless I&amp;rsquo;m sleeping elsewhere. Most often, I associate sleeping elsewhere with having time off, and having time off means I&amp;rsquo;m away from a computer screen. This frees up time for reading.&#xA;Anja had booked a suite for my birthday at Okura, and six months after I turn 33, Covid measures are finally so mild that we actually get to do it. It&amp;rsquo;s on the sixteenth floor, overlooking the Amsterdam Centre and West Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend vibes</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/10/weekend-vibes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/10/weekend-vibes/</guid>
      <description>Her Summer break started yesterday, and as always it is an event. I am so excited about getting everything right that I mostly present as a frantic killjoy. Jeopardy makes everything better.&#xA;I start today with my usual bike route past the bakeries. Niemeijer for pain au choc and canelés, followed by tiger buns and krentenbollen at Simon Meijssen. Niemeijer won best croissant of Amsterdam, but I think they&amp;rsquo;re too bready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: Home office</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/17/week-2-home-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/17/week-2-home-office/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at keeping it a secret: my favorite time in the week is when A works from home. We spent the past month building a home office in a one-bedroom apartment, and I&amp;rsquo;m happy about the result. Monday is Uni day for her. I find it endearing that her Statistics course is throwing her for a loop a little bit.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Work is so great!&amp;rdquo; I think to myself on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women&#39;s March Amsterdam</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2017/01/25/womens-march-amsterdam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2017/01/25/womens-march-amsterdam/</guid>
      <description>Proudly nasty, I joined Anja, my mother-in-law Sauci, and millions of others around the world last Saturday to attend the Women&amp;rsquo;s March. Museum Square in Amsterdam was full of pussy hats, face paint, smiling faces, and righteous indignation.&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t often attend protests, not in the last place because I&amp;rsquo;m cautious about negative media outlets that often ridicule protesters, but I loved being a part of this day. I have no idea what&amp;rsquo;s in store with this American presidency, but I imagine it can&amp;rsquo;t be very positive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
