<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>internet on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in internet on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 07:41:54 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-05-07-41-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 07:41:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-03-05-07-41-50/</guid>
      <description>I love this essay, Simone. Fully embracing the very IndieWeb concept of a personal website has helped me shake this feeling of FOMO, I imagine the same way it did for you. Don&amp;rsquo;t be hard on yourself, though, we all fell for this concept, and many of us still do. If society presents something as a way to solve a problem, most people will eventually try it. And while it does solve some problems, it also creates others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>`alt` text culture</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/13/alt-text-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/13/alt-text-culture/</guid>
      <description>More than any other time in my online life am I aware of the value of alt text. I make a point to write image descriptions whenever I can. Kind strangers with a variety of accessibility needs have been helping me understand how to best capture my interpretation of an image. I&amp;rsquo;ve come to regard alt text as the secret side bar I get to have with blind people and others who need it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The old sharing</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/13/the-old-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/13/the-old-sharing/</guid>
      <description>I am nostalgic about the way the Web used to be. I miss the handcrafted blogs that I used to visit, and the intimate windows they gave me into the lives of strangers.&#xA;I miss that I knew all the domain names by heart. It is a phantom pain of sorts; an unrest in the tip of my fingers reminding me I no longer need to make series of key combinations to find those personal public spaces, some more arts-and-craftsy than others, because most of them are gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On keeping a journal</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2012/08/31/on-keeping-a-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2012/08/31/on-keeping-a-journal/</guid>
      <description>The only journal I’ve ever been able to successfully keep is a photo journal. Not so much the one-book or one-website type, but more so a simply collection of visual anecdotes, encounters and experiences. My first website was called www.doyoulikemytightsweater.com. It was a HTML-based one-photo-per-page website that I updated very frequently. Ever since the domain expired and I got a little sick of getting pervy emails (I should have known), I had never owned a photo website that I loved so much.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
