<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>food on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in food on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 10:16:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 39: Small escapes</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/10/01/week-39-small-escapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 10:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/10/01/week-39-small-escapes/</guid>
      <description>First of all: not a great week. I continue to struggle to notice when I feel stresed or overwhelmed, and it never fails to result in my body giving me a clear sign. On Monday evening, in the midst of a busy work month, my body said &amp;ldquo;SIT. DOWN.&amp;rdquo; I needed undtil well into the weekend to feel myself again. One of the signs my body knows to give it a very mild version of conversion disorder: I lose the ability to listen to a conversation while I walk without feeling very dizzy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 33: Landing</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/20/week-33-landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/20/week-33-landing/</guid>
      <description>The first week back at work is fairly quiet, I even found myself on the verge of boredom at one point. Organically, this makes me feel bad, but I remind myself that weeks before and after holidays tend to have this effect on my life. I tell myself I&amp;rsquo;m just landing. No one can convince me the municipality of Amsterdam isn’t using major construction projects to show tourists how crap the city can be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 51: The piano</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/12/25/week-51-the-piano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/12/25/week-51-the-piano/</guid>
      <description>Happy Hanukkah and/or Christmas to those who celebrate! Even though our house is (reluctantly) multi-religious, we forgot just about every tradition we were ever taught for this time of the year. On Hanukkah Eve, Anja said &amp;ldquo;where are the tea lights?&amp;rdquo;, but we had no luck finding them to produce a makeshift chanukiah. Probably for the best. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind that we didn&amp;rsquo;t put up a Christmas tree, but I did find myself missing our outrageous ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 15: Ironic</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/17/week-15-ironic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/17/week-15-ironic/</guid>
      <description>Brushing my teeth on Friday morning, I think about the weekend ahead, secretly complaining that my social engagements will keep me from getting the rest I need. Then I remember Easter Monday. The true marker of my mid-thirties is the excitement I feel at the prospect of a bed, and nothing but it.&#xA;I hold a baby this week, one of my favorite ones. His face has two states that exist simultaneously: the one of utter shock and surprise only newborns can have, and the one that reminds you that babies know everything about the world and forget it as soon as they start to speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 13: Recruiting</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/02/week-13-recruiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/02/week-13-recruiting/</guid>
      <description>It has been snowing in Amsterdam. As the years go by, I&amp;rsquo;m having trouble understanding whether I&amp;rsquo;m experiencing the effects of global warming, or whether I&amp;rsquo;ve never paid attention to what was always in front of me until now. It is likely a combination of the two. Either way, it is sad to see Amsterdammers retreat into their homes after two weeks of shorts and drinks in the sun.&#xA;At work Leeruniek&amp;rsquo;s Product team is hiring, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the one taking care of the recruitment process for two engineering and one design role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 12: Bonsoihoir</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/03/26/week-12-bonsoihoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/03/26/week-12-bonsoihoir/</guid>
      <description>The tourists are back in town. Lots of Germans with face masks. I suppose we&amp;rsquo;re all beginning to venture out into the world again, just a bit closer to home. Anja and I are considering taking the ferry to Norway. Apparently you can camp virtually anywhere in that country, as long as you &amp;ldquo;leave it cleaner than you found it&amp;rdquo; and make sure you&amp;rsquo;re gone after two days. At this point, we&amp;rsquo;re vastly underestimating how attached we are to luxury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend vibes</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/10/weekend-vibes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/10/weekend-vibes/</guid>
      <description>Her Summer break started yesterday, and as always it is an event. I am so excited about getting everything right that I mostly present as a frantic killjoy. Jeopardy makes everything better.&#xA;I start today with my usual bike route past the bakeries. Niemeijer for pain au choc and canelés, followed by tiger buns and krentenbollen at Simon Meijssen. Niemeijer won best croissant of Amsterdam, but I think they&amp;rsquo;re too bready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 15: Streak</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/04/18/week-15-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/04/18/week-15-streak/</guid>
      <description>I am on a 33-day streak picking my teeth before bed. I&amp;rsquo;ve designed a temptation bundle, pairing the activity with a few minutes of garbage television. During these days, I&amp;rsquo;ve made it through two seasons of Love After Lockup and six seasons of Sister Wives. It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t surprise you that my watching habit has extended well beyond the time it takes me to pick my teeth. Earlier this week I decided to tone it down and return the temptation bundle to its original intention.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
