<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lists on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/lists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lists on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/lists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>33 things</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2020-12-15-33-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2020-12-15-33-things/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of thoughts, opinions, ideas, and tips that I&amp;rsquo;ve gathered in my 33rd year on Earth.&#xA;Working from home does wonders for my productivity and mental health I like the term &amp;ldquo;Torah-observant Catholic&amp;rdquo; for me Shaving my head has been one of the finest decisions I&amp;rsquo;ve made in life. I wish I could just answer &amp;lsquo;Wit Huiswerk&amp;rsquo; to most Dutch statements I hear about racism Got my first tattoo in June I listened to &amp;lsquo;Girls&amp;rsquo; by girl in red 208 times this year 🤦🏽 We got COVID-19 and it was terrifying, even without a hospital stay It&amp;rsquo;s very liberating to say &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t talk about that&amp;rdquo; when people ask small talk questions about my family or past This bolognese sauce from Smitten Kitch produces the best lasagna I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had I found a new job at a company that does great things for the world My favorite part of the pandemic, after Tiger King, was Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign team sending out a newsletter every 40 minutes on Election day It&amp;rsquo;s okay This acoustic version of Mama Kin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Rescue me&amp;rsquo; is so nice I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to speak with a Jewish family member who has become convinced that there is a satanic cabal injecting corona through 5G I will not forget the empty shelves Got my second tattoo in December I missed Paris in 2020 This pen is this year&amp;rsquo;s favorite My father died I bleached my hair I joined the leadership team of Vine &amp;amp; Fig and it is so very baller Ate Fluff for the first time My man Kit built and opened a restaurant I didn&amp;rsquo;t watch Killing Eve until now I&amp;rsquo;ve begun drinking decaffeinated coffee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Things on which I have exactly no opinion</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2012-09-26-no-opinion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2012-09-26-no-opinion/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of things I truly have no opinion on. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I have a negative opinion and I&amp;rsquo;m just sugarcoating it by saying I don&amp;rsquo;t have one. These are things of which, when I think about them, I am baffled to know they don&amp;rsquo;t trigger any form of criticism or evaluation.&#xA;Goldfish Superman Enya The Shawshank Redemption Christians The Alpes Game of Thrones Gangnam Hard towels Drug trafficking Tacos Ben &amp;amp; Jerry&amp;rsquo;s Disney World </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annual review at 36</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-12-21-annual-review-at-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-12-21-annual-review-at-36/</guid>
      <description>In one way or another, the number 36 has felt like a milestone birthday for a long time. As a tween, I imagined the glamorous autonomy that came with being 36 because I was hooked on watching the televised adventures of a foursome of privileged White women in Manhattan. Now, finally at 36, it feels important that I could&amp;rsquo;ve had a child as an adult who would now also be an adult.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
