<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I’m Zinzy Waleson Geene and this is my personal website; a quiet street on the Internet where I come to link and think. It’s a home for soft stances, lived experiences, and critical notes on the things I hold dear. You’re warmly invited to say hello.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m a mid-tier millennial I live in Amsterdam with Anja and Lemonade I&amp;rsquo;m an amateur musician and diarist I&amp;rsquo;m an advocate for the IndieWeb I was named after Nelson Mandela&amp;rsquo;s daughter Zindziswa I&amp;rsquo;m child-free I&amp;rsquo;m a non-binary lesbian (she/they) I&amp;rsquo;m neurodivergent I&amp;rsquo;ve been clean and sober since May 2018 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codex</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/pages/codex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/pages/codex/</guid>
      <description>Inspired by Buster Benson&amp;rsquo;s Codex, Greg Clarke, Elliott Cost&amp;rsquo;s Opinions and others I&amp;rsquo;m using this page to grow1 a record of things I believe.&#xA;Terms of use If you&amp;rsquo;re Zinzy No human experience can ever be summed up in a list of bullet points. Nevertheless, the things below you have written in earnest. Look at them whenever you need a reminder of what&amp;rsquo;s important to you.&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re someone else Feel free to read, learn, wonder, and remember:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/pages/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/pages/hello/</guid>
      <description>This is my hello page, where you can learn how I like to keep in touch. If you have something to share, you&amp;rsquo;d like to play or learn together, or can think of any other reason we should be talking, get in touch with me. That is a standing invitation.&#xA;How to contact me Email is your best shot: hello {@} zinzy {.} website Mastodon is also acceptable, although it may take a while LinkedIn is good for work If you&amp;rsquo;d like to schedule mentor time with me, please do so via ADPList I do not use social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My interests</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/pages/my-interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/pages/my-interests/</guid>
      <description>The red thread in my life is bottomless curiosity for the world in which we live. To learn about fleeting interests, you should read my Now page. Below is an overview of the topics that have been with me for decades.&#xA;Music Hailing from a long line of band geeks, I got my first toy piano at age four, and I haven&amp;rsquo;t been the same since. I know my way around most wind and percussion instruments, and developed a keen relationship first with the trumpet and the oboe, then the guitar, and now, finally, the piano.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/pages/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/pages/now/</guid>
      <description>Last updated in December 2023.&#xA;Here I am at Coffee Company Oosterdok, pondering what I&amp;rsquo;ll have for lunch. I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying my winter break, which I spend at museums, the library, cafes, the park. A lot of walking is involved. Like David Sedaris, I scoff at days I complete with only 10,000 steps. I just checked out three books from the library. One to fill me with spiritual familiarity, one to reacquaint me with maths, and one to help me learn Korean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Site</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/pages/site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/pages/site/</guid>
      <description>I grew up on the Internet in a time when social media meant writing comments on other people&amp;rsquo;s hand-built blogs. The sense of whimsy, endless curiosity, and a beautiful lack of information overload are highs I have been chasing ever since. It instilled in me a deep appreciation for a small-scale, intimate, and friendly internet made up of hand-crafted websites. This is one of them.&#xA;I’ve been yelling at Internet clouds since 1997.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/pages/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/pages/work/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve worked as a researcher, developer, designer, design manager, and product manager in technology companies across a variety of industries. I hold a BA in Linguistics and Literature from Utrecht University, and dropped out of seminary a decade ago. I take a Ted Lasso approach to building products: I care little about my job title, and a lot about whatever activity will help us solve problems more effectively.&#xA;Title Company Timeline Senior UX Researcher &amp;amp; Designer Gerimedica 2023 - Design &amp;amp; Product Manager Leeruniek 2020 - 2023 Lead Designer Airtrade 2015 - 2020 Designer &amp;amp; Developer Studio Zinzy 2007 - 2015 Case studies The majority of my work is protected by non-disclosure agreements.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
