<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>parks on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/parks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in parks on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/parks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Maker&#39;s marks for King&#39;s Day</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/04/25/makers-marks-for-kings-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/04/25/makers-marks-for-kings-day/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s late in the morning and I&amp;rsquo;m on my way to Gerimedica, the company&amp;rsquo;s I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be joining in May, which is next week already. I&amp;rsquo;m on my bike listening to an American podcast about the history of Dutch anarchist cycling culture.1 The scene could only be more Dutch if I had a frying pan with bitterballen on the back of my bike.&#xA;The commute is wonderful: it takes me from the East side of Amsterdam via De Pijp and Vondelpark to perhaps the most beautiful building I&amp;rsquo;ve ever had the privilege of calling my office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Come back to Chigaco</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/04/17/come-back-to-chigaco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/04/17/come-back-to-chigaco/</guid>
      <description>Spring is here, I think? I spend the afternoon in the park with ex-colleague-turned-friend Susan, who is celebrating landing a new and challenging job. There&amp;rsquo;s a boy in the park who&amp;rsquo;s walking around barefoot. Later we see him on a slack line. I like this scene; it tells me that summer is almost upon us.&#xA;I never seem skilled at enjoying whatever season is here. Instead I&amp;rsquo;m forever yearning for what&amp;rsquo;s just out of reach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking with Annelie</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/02/walking-with-annelie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/02/walking-with-annelie/</guid>
      <description>Walking with Annelie is coffee indoors today. We&amp;rsquo;ve told each other we need to go on more walks. She asks if we should dress warmly for the cold, wet park, or if we should just grab a table inside. Normally at this hour, Coffee Company is packed to the brim with digital nomads, so &amp;ldquo;dress for cold, hope for warmth&amp;rdquo; I say. Miraculously, there are two tables from which we can choose.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
