<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>piano on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/piano/</link>
    <description>Recent content in piano on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 22:49:43 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/piano/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 22:49:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/08/</guid>
      <description>Playing the piano is helping me put some puzzle pieces in the right place. I’ve always had the ability to reproduce the pitch of a song, but it wasn’t until I began playing the piano that I now seem able to identify the key by name. It may seem silly or small, but that’s a game-changer for me. It makes me feel that I can put everything together now; as though I’ve come full circle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The art of music theory</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/14/the-art-of-music-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/14/the-art-of-music-theory/</guid>
      <description>In a few days, I&amp;rsquo;ll hit my one-month mark on the piano. When I bought it and began playing, I made sure to keep an open mind about how I learn best; not following any particular method, but tailoring practices to my interests, speed, challenges, and desires.&#xA;One learning strategy that always works best for me is a top-down approach. With the piano, there&amp;rsquo;s great benefit in playing music from sheets (of which I&amp;rsquo;m capable), but I could tell something had been missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 51: The piano</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/12/25/week-51-the-piano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/12/25/week-51-the-piano/</guid>
      <description>Happy Hanukkah and/or Christmas to those who celebrate! Even though our house is (reluctantly) multi-religious, we forgot just about every tradition we were ever taught for this time of the year. On Hanukkah Eve, Anja said &amp;ldquo;where are the tea lights?&amp;rdquo;, but we had no luck finding them to produce a makeshift chanukiah. Probably for the best. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind that we didn&amp;rsquo;t put up a Christmas tree, but I did find myself missing our outrageous ornaments.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
