<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cinema on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/cinema/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cinema on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 09:16:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/cinema/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Film club S01E01</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/30/film-club-s01e01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 09:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/30/film-club-s01e01/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I attended the very first gathering of FC de Filmfanaten, a brand-new film club that my friend Jolien started. There were four of us, and we discussed the movie I was proud to have suggested: Talk To Me. I love speaking about films with others, and particularly with this diverse group of people. Everyone brought a completely unique perspective to the film, one brought film industry insights while the other had thoughtful ideas that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t considered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That was January 2023</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/31/that-was-january-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/31/that-was-january-2023/</guid>
      <description>January flew, flew by, I tell you. We started with &amp;ldquo;wow, 2023 already, let&amp;rsquo;s have a chill time this year, hey what&amp;rsquo;s on Netflix?&amp;rdquo; and at the time of writing everything is different:&#xA;Things are not chill, because we&amp;rsquo;re preparing ourselves, our lives, and our house for our first-ever puppy Both our work lives are unexpectedly bustling and busy We cancelled Netflix I&amp;rsquo;ve been saying for years that I&amp;rsquo;d be willing to pay 100 euros a month for a single, all-encompassing international streaming platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>’Love Actually’, once again</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/21/love-actually-once-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/21/love-actually-once-again/</guid>
      <description>We had two friends over today. They’re dear to me specifically because we got to know each other intimately during our eating disorder recovery. We promised we’d one day get together and watch Love Actually, much-beloved by each of us.&#xA;I’ve developed a habit of watching this film at least once a year. Despite its soft romcomness, homogenous cast, and general lack of depth it has taught me volumes on relationships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;The Whale&#39; for scale</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/11/the-whale-for-scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/11/the-whale-for-scale/</guid>
      <description>In one of the many jubilant reviews garnered by Darren Aronofsky&amp;rsquo;s latest film The Whale, one writer concluded that we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t judge a book by its cover. This was in reference to the morbidly obese main character who eventually dies, but not before we find out he developed an eating disorder out of grief. Here was a fat man who evidently had feelings despite his exterior. Ironically, I find myself doing just what the writer suggested I don&amp;rsquo;t: judge the film before I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird movies</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/10/weird-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/10/weird-movies/</guid>
      <description>I have a feeling 2023 will be the year for weird movies that steal our hearts. Look at Triangle of Sadness and White Noise. Here you have two high-budget oddball films that I&amp;rsquo;d describe not as mumblecore but coastercore, pulling you from one weird subnarrative into another, not really making up their minds about what they are, and before you&amp;rsquo;ve formed a full opinion on it, the ride is over, but you loved it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 51: The piano</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/12/25/week-51-the-piano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/12/25/week-51-the-piano/</guid>
      <description>Happy Hanukkah and/or Christmas to those who celebrate! Even though our house is (reluctantly) multi-religious, we forgot just about every tradition we were ever taught for this time of the year. On Hanukkah Eve, Anja said &amp;ldquo;where are the tea lights?&amp;rdquo;, but we had no luck finding them to produce a makeshift chanukiah. Probably for the best. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind that we didn&amp;rsquo;t put up a Christmas tree, but I did find myself missing our outrageous ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 12: Bonsoihoir</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/03/26/week-12-bonsoihoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/03/26/week-12-bonsoihoir/</guid>
      <description>The tourists are back in town. Lots of Germans with face masks. I suppose we&amp;rsquo;re all beginning to venture out into the world again, just a bit closer to home. Anja and I are considering taking the ferry to Norway. Apparently you can camp virtually anywhere in that country, as long as you &amp;ldquo;leave it cleaner than you found it&amp;rdquo; and make sure you&amp;rsquo;re gone after two days. At this point, we&amp;rsquo;re vastly underestimating how attached we are to luxury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Films about White people</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/24/films-about-white-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/24/films-about-white-people/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I&#xA;feel that I am&#xA;a&#xA;bad&#xA;Black&#xA;girl&#xA;because whenever&#xA;my white girlfriend&#xA;and I sift through&#xA;Netflix&#xA;Prime Video&#xA;or anything&#xA;with a reasonable trial&#xA;period&#xA;and she says &amp;ldquo;let&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;watch this&#xA;movie or that&amp;rdquo;&#xA;featuring Black stories&#xA;I instead&#xA;elect to watch a white&#xA;narrative&#xA;because it&amp;rsquo;s nice&#xA;to forget&#xA;about&#xA;racism&#xA;and the teacher&#xA;who called me&#xA;a monkey&#xA;and&#xA;the no one&#xA;who called him</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
