<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>being Black on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/being-black/</link>
    <description>Recent content in being Black on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/being-black/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>We all live in a white submersible</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/06/22/we-all-live-in-a-white-submersible/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/06/22/we-all-live-in-a-white-submersible/</guid>
      <description>I love a good media drama. Like a moth to a flame, or perhaps more accurately like a fly to dog poo, I am drawn to it. I check the news multiple times a day. I scoff at outlets that don&amp;rsquo;t deem it worthy of the front page. I also scoff at outlets that do. A media drama can antagonize me the way Adele disappoints me with her popularity.&#xA;The fact that I’m part of a Titanic/Titanic-obsessed gaggle of netizens somehow has me convinced I&amp;rsquo;m not just procrastinating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The game show</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/18/the-game-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/01/18/the-game-show/</guid>
      <description>This morning I got acquainted with the immigrant anxiety felt by Chinese-American journalist Jiayang Fan about her desire to speak accentless English. In an episode of one of my favorite podcasts, This American Life, Jiayang participated in a game show designed around a talent she claims to possess: the unique ability, inspired by her anxiety, to tell at what age a Chinese-American person came to the United States. The show gave her recordings of three people to prove herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meditating while Black</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/01/meditating-while-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/01/meditating-while-black/</guid>
      <description>The other day, as I was speaking about a group of queer Black designers of which I&amp;rsquo;m a part, a White lesbian asked me: &amp;ldquo;when does a group exist just so a bunch of outcasts can commiserate about their shared otherness? I mean, could someone like me join?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Great questions,&amp;rdquo; I said, &amp;ldquo;my response is identical to what you would say if someone went &amp;lsquo;why do you need lesbian bars? You don&amp;rsquo;t see me going to a straight bar, do you?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Black Lives Matter teaches me</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/04/21/what-black-lives-matter-teaches-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/04/21/what-black-lives-matter-teaches-me/</guid>
      <description> I am a Black person with privilege My privilege makes me uncomfortable I don&amp;rsquo;t want to think about racism My childhood experiences did more damage than I realized There are so many things I&amp;rsquo;ve said &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo; to that required a &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo; </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Films about White people</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/24/films-about-white-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/24/films-about-white-people/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I&#xA;feel that I am&#xA;a&#xA;bad&#xA;Black&#xA;girl&#xA;because whenever&#xA;my white girlfriend&#xA;and I sift through&#xA;Netflix&#xA;Prime Video&#xA;or anything&#xA;with a reasonable trial&#xA;period&#xA;and she says &amp;ldquo;let&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;watch this&#xA;movie or that&amp;rdquo;&#xA;featuring Black stories&#xA;I instead&#xA;elect to watch a white&#xA;narrative&#xA;because it&amp;rsquo;s nice&#xA;to forget&#xA;about&#xA;racism&#xA;and the teacher&#xA;who called me&#xA;a monkey&#xA;and&#xA;the no one&#xA;who called him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to be Black</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2018/01/01/how-to-be-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2018/01/01/how-to-be-black/</guid>
      <description>Steer clear of Adidas; obtain a degree in Dutch language and literature; wear my aunt’s glasses until I eventually need my own prescription; don&amp;rsquo;t eat fried chicken; proclaim I&amp;rsquo;m a fan of Michel Houellebecq; don&amp;rsquo;t go to a black hair salon; enrol in theological seminary; don&amp;rsquo;t listen to RnB; date a person blacker than me; date a person whiter than me; don&amp;rsquo;t eat watermelon; say I&amp;rsquo;m ‘accidentally black’ because my mother met my father while on vacation and I missed by only an inch the opportunity to be born to a white father who was a doctor, by the way; eat bananas only after I cut them into bite-size chunks that I eat with a fork, just to make sure I don’t remind anyone of a monkey; don&amp;rsquo;t listen to rap music; learn difficult words.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
