<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>productivity on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in productivity on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 09:44:15 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 09:44:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/10/</guid>
      <description> Continue a seemingly unending cycle of laundry Write in my diary Bake challah </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 09:53:34 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/03/</guid>
      <description>If you still needed convincing that I&amp;rsquo;m Grandma Tech at home, struggling to use even the most straightforward of functionalities, please be aware that I was today years old when I learned that, five years ago, TextExpander released a custom iOS keyboard that would&amp;rsquo;ve solved so many of my mundane problems, and all I was doing was asking myself &amp;ldquo;why am I even paying for that app anymore?&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking with Annelie</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/02/walking-with-annelie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/02/02/walking-with-annelie/</guid>
      <description>Walking with Annelie is coffee indoors today. We&amp;rsquo;ve told each other we need to go on more walks. She asks if we should dress warmly for the cold, wet park, or if we should just grab a table inside. Normally at this hour, Coffee Company is packed to the brim with digital nomads, so &amp;ldquo;dress for cold, hope for warmth&amp;rdquo; I say. Miraculously, there are two tables from which we can choose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Summer Christmas</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2013/12/30/indian-summer-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2013/12/30/indian-summer-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Christmas break is passing by me like it passes by an ambitious teenager. I greeted all the things I could do with great enthusiasm. Sadly, that feeling quickly turned into terror once I realised two weeks isn’t that long and I need to sleep.&#xA;Productivity-wise, man can only fail under such conditions, this I know.&#xA;Meanwhile, I keep being amazed by the weather in Haarlem. I managed to take some photos downtown last week that remind me of the beginning of September, despite a winter coat here and rain hat there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commonplace book</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2013/12/20/commonplace-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2013/12/20/commonplace-book/</guid>
      <description>Ryan Holiday describes the how and why of his ‘Commonplace Book’, a collection of quotes and other pieces of text written down on index cards. I, too, have been keeping such a system since I started college. I always carry a few cards when I’m out and about, held together by bulldog clips.&#xA;Incredibly handy and simple, it has turned out.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
