<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>television on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in television on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 27: Haven</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/07/09/week-27-haven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/07/09/week-27-haven/</guid>
      <description>This week, I attended my first Gerimedica party. It’s great to know I can expect a big celebration every year, and not just for the company’s sweet sixteen. It confirmed what I already know: great vibe, great taste, great people. I went to Bar Bario on Saturday for a meet-up called Hair Haven, which fosters connection between people with curly hair. Again, I was struck by how welcoming the space is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 11: Meeting Patrick</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/26/week-11-meeting-patrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/26/week-11-meeting-patrick/</guid>
      <description>I got to meet one of my Internet heroes this week: Patrick Rhone and his family were on a Europe trip, and I was lucky enough to catch the planning stage on his blog right in time to extend an invitation. We spent a rainy Monday evening in de Jordaan at Cafe de Tuin, talking ye olde Internet productivity culture, the arts, politics, hopes and dreams, and how his teenage daughter apparently woke up one night singing &amp;ldquo;raise a glass to freedom&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 12:57:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/12/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 07:35:06 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/12/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve begun rewatching Succession again to prepare for its fourth and final season. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched it yet, it is a pure Shakespearean spectacle worth every second. Never before had I seen a work of fiction in which every single character is an antagonist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 10: Outings</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/12/week-10-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/12/week-10-outings/</guid>
      <description>It snowed a few times this week and I was as baffled as I always am to see it happening in March. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a great understanding of what the weather&amp;rsquo;s supposed to do in a given period of the year. After two weeks of cocooning, we&amp;rsquo;ve finally been taking Lemonade out to various places. I aim to take her out at least once a day, usually to the park or a walk around the block.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend vibes</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/10/weekend-vibes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/07/10/weekend-vibes/</guid>
      <description>Her Summer break started yesterday, and as always it is an event. I am so excited about getting everything right that I mostly present as a frantic killjoy. Jeopardy makes everything better.&#xA;I start today with my usual bike route past the bakeries. Niemeijer for pain au choc and canelés, followed by tiger buns and krentenbollen at Simon Meijssen. Niemeijer won best croissant of Amsterdam, but I think they&amp;rsquo;re too bready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 15: Streak</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/04/18/week-15-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/04/18/week-15-streak/</guid>
      <description>I am on a 33-day streak picking my teeth before bed. I&amp;rsquo;ve designed a temptation bundle, pairing the activity with a few minutes of garbage television. During these days, I&amp;rsquo;ve made it through two seasons of Love After Lockup and six seasons of Sister Wives. It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t surprise you that my watching habit has extended well beyond the time it takes me to pick my teeth. Earlier this week I decided to tone it down and return the temptation bundle to its original intention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Films about White people</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/24/films-about-white-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/24/films-about-white-people/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I&#xA;feel that I am&#xA;a&#xA;bad&#xA;Black&#xA;girl&#xA;because whenever&#xA;my white girlfriend&#xA;and I sift through&#xA;Netflix&#xA;Prime Video&#xA;or anything&#xA;with a reasonable trial&#xA;period&#xA;and she says &amp;ldquo;let&amp;rsquo;s&#xA;watch this&#xA;movie or that&amp;rdquo;&#xA;featuring Black stories&#xA;I instead&#xA;elect to watch a white&#xA;narrative&#xA;because it&amp;rsquo;s nice&#xA;to forget&#xA;about&#xA;racism&#xA;and the teacher&#xA;who called me&#xA;a monkey&#xA;and&#xA;the no one&#xA;who called him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: Home office</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/17/week-2-home-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/17/week-2-home-office/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at keeping it a secret: my favorite time in the week is when A works from home. We spent the past month building a home office in a one-bedroom apartment, and I&amp;rsquo;m happy about the result. Monday is Uni day for her. I find it endearing that her Statistics course is throwing her for a loop a little bit.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Work is so great!&amp;rdquo; I think to myself on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
