<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>neurodivergence on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/neurodivergence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in neurodivergence on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/neurodivergence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Walking with Annelie</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-02-02-walking-with-annelie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-02-02-walking-with-annelie/</guid>
      <description>Walking with Annelie is coffee indoors today. We&amp;rsquo;ve told each other we need to go on more walks. She asks if we should dress warmly for the cold, wet park, or if we should just grab a table inside. Normally at this hour, Coffee Company is packed to the brim with digital nomads, so &amp;ldquo;dress for cold, hope for warmth&amp;rdquo; I say. Miraculously, there are two tables from which we can choose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That was January 2023</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-31-that-was-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-31-that-was-january/</guid>
      <description>January flew, flew by, I tell you. We started with &amp;ldquo;wow, 2023 already, let&amp;rsquo;s have a chill time this year, hey what&amp;rsquo;s on Netflix?&amp;rdquo; and at the time of writing everything is different:&#xA;Things are not chill, because we&amp;rsquo;re preparing ourselves, our lives, and our house for our first-ever puppy Both our work lives are unexpectedly bustling and busy We cancelled Netflix I&amp;rsquo;ve been saying for years that I&amp;rsquo;d be willing to pay 100 euros a month for a single, all-encompassing international streaming platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-recognizer</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-20-super-recognizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-20-super-recognizer/</guid>
      <description>On occasion, Anja will compliment me on my ability to recognize people. I don’t know when I first noticed it myself, but there are actors I recognize even if they played minor characters in an episode of a show I watched 15 years ago. Or I might point out that woman I saw on the bus before COVID hit to a confused Anja.&#xA;I’m learning it’s not a very common trait because of the scoffing sound I make whenever Anja confuses Keira Knightly and Daisy Ridley, or Michelle Pfeiffer and Meg Ryan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The art of music theory</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-14-the-art-of-music-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-14-the-art-of-music-theory/</guid>
      <description>In a few days, I&amp;rsquo;ll hit my one-month mark on the piano. When I bought it and began playing, I made sure to keep an open mind about how I learn best; not following any particular method, but tailoring practices to my interests, speed, challenges, and desires.&#xA;One learning strategy that always works best for me is a top-down approach. With the piano, there&amp;rsquo;s great benefit in playing music from sheets (of which I&amp;rsquo;m capable), but I could tell something had been missing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
