<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>weeknotes on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/weeknotes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in weeknotes on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/weeknotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: Omek</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2024/01/14/week-2-omek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2024/01/14/week-2-omek/</guid>
      <description>Codex&#xA;This week marked the week I got back into the swing of things at work. I tend to find the holiday season quite boring because things slow down quite a bit. Now that people are returning from their winter break, my to do list is filling up again with exciting projects, opportunities for collaboration, and research endeavors. As usual, a conversation with my manager reminded me how much I love my job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 1: Miracle mornings</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2024/01/07/week-1-miracle-mornings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2024/01/07/week-1-miracle-mornings/</guid>
      <description>A somewhat quiet week, mostly spent at the office because Anja&amp;rsquo;s on winter break, although I did enjoy spending time at Coffee Company Oosterdok as well. Working without my regular laptop stand and wireless keyboard and trackpad doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel great for my body, but they make great coffee. I seem to have found my way back to the [[Miracle morning|Miracle morning]] method. While I cringe at the very notion of self development, it has been great to start my day in quietude.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 47: Geert Milders</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/11/25/week-47-geert-milders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 10:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/11/25/week-47-geert-milders/</guid>
      <description>Covid It&amp;rsquo;s curious to see my response to a bout of Covid is not much different from what it was in early 2020. Despite a negative test, symptoms tell me everything I need to know. I have to remind myself every day this week that, given the regulations, I&amp;rsquo;m not obliged to quarantine. Nevertheless, Anja and I are both barely able to walk the dog. I work half days, and spend my afternoons in bed with hot water bottles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 46: Osama</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/11/19/week-46-osama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 10:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/11/19/week-46-osama/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m making an attempt this week to make my weeknotes more of a personal record rather than a performance of how exciting my week is. What I&amp;rsquo;ve written answers the question I might ask myself seven years from now: what was life like this week? I went on the road for on-site research on Tuesday, and was delighted by the particular nursing home that we visited. It seems many Dutch healthcare organizations have understood that environments that resemble the real-life environments of patients contribute to their overall wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 39: Small escapes</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/10/01/week-39-small-escapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 10:16:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/10/01/week-39-small-escapes/</guid>
      <description>First of all: not a great week. I continue to struggle to notice when I feel stresed or overwhelmed, and it never fails to result in my body giving me a clear sign. On Monday evening, in the midst of a busy work month, my body said &amp;ldquo;SIT. DOWN.&amp;rdquo; I needed undtil well into the weekend to feel myself again. One of the signs my body knows to give it a very mild version of conversion disorder: I lose the ability to listen to a conversation while I walk without feeling very dizzy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 37: Rosh Hashanah</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/17/week-37-rosh-hashanah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 08:49:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/17/week-37-rosh-hashanah/</guid>
      <description>Cooler temperatures! After the hottest week I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced in months, things were back to comfortable Summer weather. By the time I&amp;rsquo;m writing this the sky is gray and it&amp;rsquo;s raining, but this week&amp;rsquo;s weather was cheerful and moderate. On Tuesday and Wednesday I gave two big UX workshops at week to help coworkers understand how they can use UX in their daily work. I&amp;rsquo;ve been giving workshops for well over a decade, always trusting my instinct to figure out what a particular group or context required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 36: Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/10/week-36-homecoming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:21:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/09/10/week-36-homecoming/</guid>
      <description>IT IS HOT STOP CLIMATE CHANGE NOW. I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve seen hotter days this year than week 36. Getting out of a hot shower and feeling equally wet fifteen minutes later. Lemonade barely wanting to walk outside. The sun beaming so feriously we can&amp;rsquo;t keep the windows open. Thank you, Jesus, but please make it cooler. There&amp;rsquo;s something sweet about seeing Amsterdam through the eyes of friends from abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 34: Somerlust</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/27/week-34-somerlust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:49:15 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/27/week-34-somerlust/</guid>
      <description>Met [[Tim Bleeker|Tim Bleeker]] at [[Somerlust Park|Somerlust Park]] on [[2023-08-22|Tuesday]], a get-together that started as &amp;ldquo;chilling in the park&amp;rdquo;, and which turned into grabbing a drink at l&amp;rsquo;Osteria. The venue is not one I can recommend. When requesting a bigger table because more people would be coming, the waiter scoffed at us. Then he closed the red velvet roped entrance. Later, his colleague told me people often just barge into the venue, ignoring waiters&amp;rsquo; requests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 33: Landing</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/20/week-33-landing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/08/20/week-33-landing/</guid>
      <description>The first week back at work is fairly quiet, I even found myself on the verge of boredom at one point. Organically, this makes me feel bad, but I remind myself that weeks before and after holidays tend to have this effect on my life. I tell myself I&amp;rsquo;m just landing. No one can convince me the municipality of Amsterdam isn’t using major construction projects to show tourists how crap the city can be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 27: Haven</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/07/09/week-27-haven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/07/09/week-27-haven/</guid>
      <description>This week, I attended my first Gerimedica party. It’s great to know I can expect a big celebration every year, and not just for the company’s sweet sixteen. It confirmed what I already know: great vibe, great taste, great people. I went to Bar Bario on Saturday for a meet-up called Hair Haven, which fosters connection between people with curly hair. Again, I was struck by how welcoming the space is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 26: Keti Koti</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/07/01/week-26-keti-koti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/07/01/week-26-keti-koti/</guid>
      <description>Two months of onboarding have rushed by in a blink. The new job is absolutely wonderful: the people are great, the work is complex and important, and the office itself is perhaps the finest I&amp;rsquo;ve ever worked at. I joined this company because the challenges they have seemed interesting to me. I&amp;rsquo;m very pleased that, two months in, it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to think that, at one point in time, these challenges weren&amp;rsquo;t also mine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 11: Meeting Patrick</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/26/week-11-meeting-patrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/26/week-11-meeting-patrick/</guid>
      <description>I got to meet one of my Internet heroes this week: Patrick Rhone and his family were on a Europe trip, and I was lucky enough to catch the planning stage on his blog right in time to extend an invitation. We spent a rainy Monday evening in de Jordaan at Cafe de Tuin, talking ye olde Internet productivity culture, the arts, politics, hopes and dreams, and how his teenage daughter apparently woke up one night singing &amp;ldquo;raise a glass to freedom&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 10: Outings</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/12/week-10-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023/03/12/week-10-outings/</guid>
      <description>It snowed a few times this week and I was as baffled as I always am to see it happening in March. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a great understanding of what the weather&amp;rsquo;s supposed to do in a given period of the year. After two weeks of cocooning, we&amp;rsquo;ve finally been taking Lemonade out to various places. I aim to take her out at least once a day, usually to the park or a walk around the block.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 51: The piano</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/12/25/week-51-the-piano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/12/25/week-51-the-piano/</guid>
      <description>Happy Hanukkah and/or Christmas to those who celebrate! Even though our house is (reluctantly) multi-religious, we forgot just about every tradition we were ever taught for this time of the year. On Hanukkah Eve, Anja said &amp;ldquo;where are the tea lights?&amp;rdquo;, but we had no luck finding them to produce a makeshift chanukiah. Probably for the best. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind that we didn&amp;rsquo;t put up a Christmas tree, but I did find myself missing our outrageous ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 47: Booster</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/11/27/week-47-booster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/11/27/week-47-booster/</guid>
      <description>I forgot how the COVID booster can make you feel as though, temporarily, the world may well be ending. I got it earlier this week, and it left me with a sore arm and that dreadful, ridiculous sensation that accompanies a flu that lasts a week too long. I mimic my late stepfather, who used to wimper like a puppy whenever he got a cold. I still do well to limit my hours of screen time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 44: Coat</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/11/06/week-44-coat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/11/06/week-44-coat/</guid>
      <description>The weather has officially reached a temperature that requires me to buy a new coat. I dread it. Unlike most other types of clothing, coats and jackets never seem to suit me, regardless of the style. To soften the blow of having to order several coats on the Internet hoping one will work for me, I granted myself three sets of retro socks.&#xA;I finished reading The Midnight Library, which I had borrowed from Annelie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 16: Springtime holidays</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/23/week-16-springtime-holidays/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/23/week-16-springtime-holidays/</guid>
      <description>Each year I&amp;rsquo;m less embarrassed to say it: I don&amp;rsquo;t like that stretch of time during the Dutch Springtime when no work week is normal. Aside from the usual Christian holidays there&amp;rsquo;s King&amp;rsquo;s Day and Liberation Day, and I&amp;rsquo;ve found it really messes with my head. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind them much looking ahead (like I did last week, but having to live through it could well be too much for me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 15: Ironic</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/17/week-15-ironic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/17/week-15-ironic/</guid>
      <description>Brushing my teeth on Friday morning, I think about the weekend ahead, secretly complaining that my social engagements will keep me from getting the rest I need. Then I remember Easter Monday. The true marker of my mid-thirties is the excitement I feel at the prospect of a bed, and nothing but it.&#xA;I hold a baby this week, one of my favorite ones. His face has two states that exist simultaneously: the one of utter shock and surprise only newborns can have, and the one that reminds you that babies know everything about the world and forget it as soon as they start to speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 13: Recruiting</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/02/week-13-recruiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/04/02/week-13-recruiting/</guid>
      <description>It has been snowing in Amsterdam. As the years go by, I&amp;rsquo;m having trouble understanding whether I&amp;rsquo;m experiencing the effects of global warming, or whether I&amp;rsquo;ve never paid attention to what was always in front of me until now. It is likely a combination of the two. Either way, it is sad to see Amsterdammers retreat into their homes after two weeks of shorts and drinks in the sun.&#xA;At work Leeruniek&amp;rsquo;s Product team is hiring, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been the one taking care of the recruitment process for two engineering and one design role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 12: Bonsoihoir</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022/03/26/week-12-bonsoihoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022/03/26/week-12-bonsoihoir/</guid>
      <description>The tourists are back in town. Lots of Germans with face masks. I suppose we&amp;rsquo;re all beginning to venture out into the world again, just a bit closer to home. Anja and I are considering taking the ferry to Norway. Apparently you can camp virtually anywhere in that country, as long as you &amp;ldquo;leave it cleaner than you found it&amp;rdquo; and make sure you&amp;rsquo;re gone after two days. At this point, we&amp;rsquo;re vastly underestimating how attached we are to luxury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 15: Streak</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/04/18/week-15-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/04/18/week-15-streak/</guid>
      <description>I am on a 33-day streak picking my teeth before bed. I&amp;rsquo;ve designed a temptation bundle, pairing the activity with a few minutes of garbage television. During these days, I&amp;rsquo;ve made it through two seasons of Love After Lockup and six seasons of Sister Wives. It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t surprise you that my watching habit has extended well beyond the time it takes me to pick my teeth. Earlier this week I decided to tone it down and return the temptation bundle to its original intention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 2: Home office</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/17/week-2-home-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021/01/17/week-2-home-office/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m terrible at keeping it a secret: my favorite time in the week is when A works from home. We spent the past month building a home office in a one-bedroom apartment, and I&amp;rsquo;m happy about the result. Monday is Uni day for her. I find it endearing that her Statistics course is throwing her for a loop a little bit.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Work is so great!&amp;rdquo; I think to myself on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunday seeds</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2013/12/22/sunday-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2013/12/22/sunday-seeds/</guid>
      <description>If you ever happen to find yourself in the sleepy fishing town of IJmuiden: the fish, service, atmosphere, and cheesecake in the fish restaurant De Meerplaats are all very pleasant. For my birthday, Erica Bouma gave me Jesus by rebel theologian Hans Küng. It’s a great and easy read — a recommendation for anybody interested in the history of Christianity. The Son and the Stranger is a beautiful Dutch-language documentary about Daan, a man who, after studying Hebrew in university, converted to the ultra orthodox Jewish faith.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
