<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reading on Zinzy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>https://zinzy.website/tags/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reading on Zinzy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zinzy.website/tags/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 33: Landing</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-08-20-week-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-08-20-week-33/</guid>
      <description>The first week back at work is fairly quiet, I even found myself on the verge of boredom at one point. Organically, this makes me feel bad, but I remind myself that weeks before and after holidays tend to have this effect on my life. I tell myself I&amp;rsquo;m just landing. No one can convince me the municipality of Amsterdam isn’t using major construction projects to show tourists how crap the city can be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 26: Keti Koti</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-07-01-week-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-07-01-week-26/</guid>
      <description>Two months of onboarding have rushed by in a blink. The new job is absolutely wonderful: the people are great, the work is complex and important, and the office itself is perhaps the finest I&amp;rsquo;ve ever worked at. I joined this company because the challenges they have seemed interesting to me. I&amp;rsquo;m very pleased that, two months in, it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to think that, at one point in time, these challenges weren&amp;rsquo;t also mine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That was January 2023</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-31-that-was-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2023-01-31-that-was-january/</guid>
      <description>January flew, flew by, I tell you. We started with &amp;ldquo;wow, 2023 already, let&amp;rsquo;s have a chill time this year, hey what&amp;rsquo;s on Netflix?&amp;rdquo; and at the time of writing everything is different:&#xA;Things are not chill, because we&amp;rsquo;re preparing ourselves, our lives, and our house for our first-ever puppy Both our work lives are unexpectedly bustling and busy We cancelled Netflix I&amp;rsquo;ve been saying for years that I&amp;rsquo;d be willing to pay 100 euros a month for a single, all-encompassing international streaming platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 44: Coat</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2022-11-06-week-44/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2022-11-06-week-44/</guid>
      <description>The weather has officially reached a temperature that requires me to buy a new coat. I dread it. Unlike most other types of clothing, coats and jackets never seem to suit me, regardless of the style. To soften the blow of having to order several coats on the Internet hoping one will work for me, I granted myself three sets of retro socks.&#xA;I finished reading The Midnight Library, which I had borrowed from Annelie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A believable truth</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2021-07-18-a-believable-truth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2021-07-18-a-believable-truth/</guid>
      <description>I never get much reading done unless I&amp;rsquo;m sleeping elsewhere. Most often, I associate sleeping elsewhere with having time off, and having time off means I&amp;rsquo;m away from a computer screen. This frees up time for reading.&#xA;Anja had booked a suite for my birthday at Okura, and six months after I turn 33, Covid measures are finally so mild that we actually get to do it. It&amp;rsquo;s on the sixteenth floor, overlooking the Amsterdam Centre and West Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunday seeds</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2013-12-22-sunday-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2013-12-22-sunday-seeds/</guid>
      <description>If you ever happen to find yourself in the sleepy fishing town of IJmuiden: the fish, service, atmosphere, and cheesecake in the fish restaurant De Meerplaats are all very pleasant. For my birthday, Erica Bouma gave me Jesus by rebel theologian Hans Küng. It’s a great and easy read — a recommendation for anybody interested in the history of Christianity. The Son and the Stranger is a beautiful Dutch-language documentary about Daan, a man who, after studying Hebrew in university, converted to the ultra orthodox Jewish faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading list</title>
      <link>https://zinzy.website/2012-08-10-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zinzy.website/2012-08-10-reading-list/</guid>
      <description> Essex Country by Jeff Lemire Ergens Waar Je Niet Wil Zijn (Wrong Place) by Brecht Evens Box Office Poison by Alex Robinson Lucille by Ludivic Debeurme Swallow Me Whole by Nate Powell 120 Days of Simon by Simon Gärdenfors Underwire by Jennifer Hayden The Playwright by Daren White and Eddie Campbell Any Empire by Nate Powell Lost Dogs by Jeff Lemire </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
